Muhammad Usama Ali

Rawalpindi 46010 usama1.business@gmail.com +92 336 0525011

Being a disciple of the Software Engineering, I have been engaged in learning new Technologies App development, Machine Learning for last few years.

In future, my research will focus on improvement and innovation in learning Data analytics based Academic Decision Support Systems. As Student, I would like to serve my Field, in building an Ethics & Knowledge based personality, focus on Innovation and creativity.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Flutter developer

whizpool - G8 Islamabad June 2021 to Present

Working on existing products and new client based projects,
Worked on buying and selling store Vantoca App, reporting product.
Participates into: Code cleaning, Bug fixing, code reviewing, app uploading.
Worked on Quran app, Quran Tutor App and Vantoca app (Buying/Selling marketplace).

CSR

Ace Solutions - Rawalpindi, PK July 2020 to December 2020

• Worked on multiple projects Home insurance, Auto insurance and Home improvements.

Education

Bachelor's in Software Engineering

Foundation University Rawalpindi Campus - Rawalpindi September 2016 to September 2021

Intermediate in Computer Science

Global College Of Science - Rawalpindi August 2014 to September 2016

TensorFlow Summit 2019 Participation Certificate (National Incubation Centre) in Machine Learning

NIC - Islamabad

Skills

- Strong Knowledge of Object Oriented Programming
- Telemarketing
- Communication Skills
- Android App Development.

Links

https://github.com/Usama1Ace

Certifications and Licenses

MERN Bootcamp Certificate

Present

- Learnt new javascript techstack.
- Got grip on fundamental on MERN stack.
- Completed one MERN project during bootcamp.